{
    "subject": "Queen_Paola_of_Belgium",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Albert_II_of_Belgium",
    "human_readable": "Queen Paola of Belgium is married to Albert II of Belgium.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9719976782798767,
            "question": "Who is Queen Paola of Belgium married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9602600336074829,
            "question": "To whom is Albert II of Belgium married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9073314666748047,
            "question": "What is the name of the Belgian king who is married to Queen Paola?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8944271802902222,
            "question": "Are Albert II and Queen Paola still married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8327363729476929,
            "question": "Is Queen Paola related to King Albert II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6631330847740173,
            "question": "Who is the queen of Belgium?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5123084187507629,
            "question": "What country do Queen Paola and King Albert II rule?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48026421666145325,
            "question": "What is the name of Belgium's queen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28589650988578796,
            "question": "Is Albert II a king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22425192594528198,
            "question": "What is the name of the Belgian monarch who is currently in power?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Queen Paola of Belgium is married to Albert II of Belgium.",
            "html": "yago_28926_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Albert II a king?",
            "html": "yago_28926_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Belgium's queen?",
            "html": "yago_28926_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country do Queen Paola and King Albert II rule?",
            "html": "yago_28926_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28926_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28926_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28926_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28926_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28926_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28926_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28926_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28926_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28926_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28926_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide strong evidence that supports the triple. The various files (4.txt, 1.txt, 12.txt, 78.txt, 39.txt, and 14.txt) all mention Queen Paola of Belgium being married to Albert II of Belgium, with specific dates and details about their marriage, children, and reign as King and Queen of the Belgians."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Queen Paola of Belgium is married to Albert II of Belgium.\" The details about their marriage, including the date (July 2, 1959), where they met (Vatican during the coronation of Pope John XXIII in 1958), and the fact that Paola became Queen of the Belgians upon Albert's ascension to the throne are all consistent with the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}